http://www.thegraphicedge.com/privacy-policy

COVID-19 Update: Learn about the steps we are taking to protect our communities and how it will impact our service. Click here.
Search
Search...
T-Shirt Designer
Design T-shirts, Sweatshirts, and Polos Online!
Our t-shirt designer makes it easy to create custom apparel for all occasions. Share your designs in social media and order enough for everyone.
Select Your Decoration Method:
Screen Printing
Bright, vibrant colors printable on a huge variety of shirt styles and fabrics. Be sure to explore Distressed and Vintage options.
Embroidery
Your logo, mascot, name, or other design stitched in colorful thread.
CorporateBusiness WearPromotional ProductsBagsDecals & StickersSigns & BannersView All CategoriesBusiness WearView AllMenWomenSafety GearWork JacketsCorporate OuterwearPromotional ProductsView AllChairsDrinkwareKooziesNoveltyLanyardsPensDesk & OfficeBagsView AllBriefcases and MessengersBackpacksSack Packs and Gym SacksTote BagsDecals & StickersView AllSigns & BannersView AllView All CategoriesView AllBusiness WearPromotional ProductsBagsTeam Sales
Coaches Resources
TEAM STORES
TEAM STORE APPAREL
COACHES APPAREL
FIND YOUR REP
CLINIC CALENDAR
Team Uniforms, Accessories, and Resources.
Football
Volleyball
Basketball
Baseball
Softball
Soccer
Cross Country
Wrestling
Track
Golf
Lacrosse
Cheerleading
CatalogT-ShirtsView By SportOuterwearSweatsCloseout SpecialsCaps & VisorsWomen's StylesPolosDesign OnlinePants/ShortsWhat's NewBagsYouth StylesView All CategoriesT-ShirtsView AllShort SleeveLong SleeveTank Tops & SleevelessLadies Short SleeveLadies Long SleeveLadies Tanks & SleevelessYouth Short SleeveYouth Long SleeveYouth Tanks & SleevelessCamp SetsView By SportView AllFootballVolleyballBasketballBaseballSoftballSoccerTrackWrestlingLacrosseCross CountryDanceCheerleadingGolfOuterwearView All1/4 ZipsTeam JacketsWarm Up SuitsWindbreakers and Rain JacketsSherpa JacketsFleece JacketsSoftshell JacketsWork JacketsVestsInsulated JacketsSweatsView AllHoodiesCrew SweatshirtsFull Zip1/4 ZipsSweatpantsCloseout SpecialsView AllT-ShirtsPolosSweatsOuterwearPantsShortsAccessoriesShoe OutletFootball CloseoutBasketball CloseoutVolleyball CloseoutBaseball CloseoutCaps & VisorsView AllCapsBoonie/Bucket HatsVisorsBeaniesWomen's StylesView AllT-ShirtsSweatsOuterwearPolosSweatersWomen's BottomsCustom Printed Sports BrasPolosView AllDesign OnlineMen's PolosWomen's PolosYouth PolosLong Sleeve PolosPerformance PolosDesign OnlineView AllT-ShirtsLong Sleeve T-ShirtsTanks & SleevelessHoodiesCrewsLayeringOuterwearPolosDress ShirtsCasual ShirtsWork ShirtsWork JacketsSafety GearBagsBeaniesCaps & HatsShortsPants/ShortsView AllPerformance ShortsMesh ShortsSweat PantsCompression Leggings & ShortsCasual Pants & ShortsDress Pants & ShortsWork PantsWhat's NewView AllUnder ArmourThe North FaceCarharttHollowayBagsView AllBackpacksSackpacksDuffelsBriefcases & MessengersTotesYouth StylesView AllT-ShirtsSweatsPants & ShortsYouth PolosOuterwearUniformsHeadwearView All CategoriesView AllTeam UniformsTeam Sports EquipmentDesign OnlineWhat's New!Closeout SpecialsT-ShirtsSweatsPants & ShortsPolosSweatersOuterwearWomen's StylesYouth StylesInfant & ToddlerSublimated Spirit WearCustom HeadwearAccessoriesBagsShoesStadium ChairsPromotionalSafety GearCoaching ApparelReferee ZoneCorporateMade in America T-Shirts, Sweatshirts, and ApparelLetterman JacketsStickersBannersUnder Armour Teamadidas TeamREGLETEKInfection PreventionDesign LibraryScreen PrintingEmbroideryHeat PressAppliqueRhinestonesLaser EtchBanner DesignsDecals, Stickers & ClingsWall DecalsView All CategoriesScreen PrintingView AllInteractive TemplatesSportsSpirit WearBooster ClubCheerleading Shirt DesignsVintageSchool DaysArtsOutdoor PursuitsFight Against CancerFirst RespondersPatrioticOther DesignsFull-Color Process ScreenprintsHolidaysAdidasCorporateMotorsportsSpecial LocationsGlow In The DarkEmbroideryView AllInteractiveArtsSportsCheerleadingSchool DaysCorporateFirst RespondersHeadwearSpirit WearBooster ClubOutdoor PursuitsMotorsportsV-NotchOtherHeat PressView AllAppliqueView AllUA Appliqueadidas AppliqueRhinestonesView AllLaser EtchView AllBanner DesignsView AllDecals, Stickers & ClingsView AllHelmet DecalsStickersBumper StickersWindow ClingsWall DecalsView AllView All CategoriesView AllScreen PrintingEmbroideryAppliqueHeat PressBanner DesignsDecals, Stickers, ClingsWall DecalsDigital PrintingRhinestonesLaser EtchTackle TwillApplique/Tackle TwillCatalog ArtLaser CutAbout Us
Why The Graphic Edge?
The Graphic Edge is a leader in custom screen printing and embroidery, having produced millions of customized garments for thousands of teams, schools, organizations, businesses, and individuals since 1989.
Each and every day we strive to provide the highest level of customer service and the highest quality screen printing and embroidery for your garments. That's why your satisfaction is always 100% guaranteed.
Learn More About The Graphic Edge
Services We Offer
Company History
Mission Statement
Our Promise To You
Career Opportunities
Contact Us
We'd Love To Hear From You!
Need help? Have questions? Let's get you in touch with the right person!
Contact a Sales Rep
Teams, Schools, and Individuals
Club Sports, Umpires, and Referees
Corporate/Business Wear
Military
Customer Service
Email Customer Service
Call Customer Service: 1-800-747-9744
Shorts
What's New!
Under Armour
The North Face
Carhartt
Holloway
Closeout Specials
T-Shirts
Polos
Sweats
Privacy Policy
Information Collection • Information Usage • Information Protection • Cookie Usage • Third Party Disclosure • Third Party Links
Google AdSense • CalOPPA • COPPA • Fair Information Practices • CAN SPAM • Our Contact Information
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
We do not collect information from visitors of our site.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To improve our website in order to better serve you.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
To quickly process your transactions.
To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use "cookies?"
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
Keep track of advertisements.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders .
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
Demographics and Interests Reporting
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy page
Users are able to change their personal information by logging in to their account
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify the users via email within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred
To be in accordance with CAN SPAM we agree to the following:
NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Be the first to learn about upcoming sales, special offers and new products.
155 Seward Rd.
® 2020 The Graphic Edge. All rights reserved.
WEB DEVELOPMENT BY
GLOBAL REACH
